# Clyde James Felix

Phone: 808 546 9976 Email: felixclyde@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/felixclyde Website: cjfelixx.github.io

# Summary

Graduate Electrical Engineering student with experience at academic and professional research in Image processing & Computer Vision, Medical Image computing, and Machine Learning/Deep Learning science. Skilled in Computer programming, Statistical Modeling, Technical Writing, and utilizing research methodologies.

## Education

## Master of Science in Electrical Engineering

Aug 2020 - Expected: May 2021

University of Hawaii at Manoa Track: Systems and Data Science

## Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering

Aug 2016 - May 2020

University of Hawaii at Manoa GPA: 3.45/4.0, Major GPA: 3.64

# **Skills**

#### Tools:

Unix/Linux, C, Java, Python, MATLAB,, HTML/CSS, Git, LaTeX, Visual Studio, Microsoft Office Projects that utilized the skills above can be found here: <a href="https://github.com/cjfelixx">https://github.com/cjfelixx</a>

# **Work Experiences**

## **GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT**

UH Manoa Department of Electrical Engineering

Aug 2020 - Present

- Conduct graduate level research in Data Science, Image Processing & Computer Vision, medical image computing using Machine Learning and AI.
- Utilized Pytorch to develop an Iterative Deep Learning algorithm for MRI Image Reconstruction.

## **TEACHING ASSISTANT**

UH Manoa Department of Electrical Engineering

Jan 2020 - Present

- EE 415, Digital Signal Processing. Mentored students on applying Digital Signal Processing concepts in MATLAB.
- EE 345, Linear Algebra & Machine Learning. Taught basic Python with Linear Algebra and Machine Learning applications.

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN**

Alohapay Inc.

Mar 2020 - May 2020

- Provided Quality Assurance by implementing and testing Python test scripts with Selenium.
- Composed and organized documentation on testing reports and user manual on company procedures.

# UNDERGRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

UH Manoa Department of Physics & Astronomy

May 2019 - July 2020

- Conducted experiments using radioactive sources to study the development of efficient Neutron detectors.
- Utilized Linux and Python scripts to provide data visualizations of experimental results.

## **UNDERGRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT**

**UH Manoa Department of Mathematics** 

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Collaborated with undergraduate students on Automatic Complexities, VC-dimensions, and the Fibonacci/Tribonacci sequences using Python.
- Contributed to an accepted ISAIM conference paper and Undergraduate Research Program presentations for the theoretical findings.

## **EXCHANGE STUDENT RESEARCHER**

Tokyo University of Agriculture & Technology

Jul 2019 - Aug 2019

- Designed a MATLAB code of a Brain-Computer Interface Machine Learnings model that classifies Motor Imagery tasks.
- Successfully determined a better Motor Imagery setting that will benefit stroke rehabilitation studies.